Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hi. my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me. but I have something
to tell you that's going to sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're going
to believe me because
you're very good at
telling when I'm lying.
Eevee. can you check the calibration of my
targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed into me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey. Eevee. take five.
Standing five.
We used to know each other.
We were together. but something bad was
going to happen.
And the only way to stop it was to make
everyone forget me.
First hit and my tears go!
Oh my gosh. we're here. we made it!
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest you've
ever been in your entire life right now.
I can't.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
And sometimes Spider-Man
has to do the hard
thing. even if it breaks
Peter Parker's heart.
And maybe that's my responsibility.
to live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope that deep down something inside
of you remembers that you loved me too.
But until then. I'm just going to be
Spider-Man.
Members of the Man
spreading crime in the
end were apprehended
by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey. you live on the same tour?
Oh. hi.
Cool.
Doesn't anybody ever come up here?
Unless they like the specialist.
We've just been using it for storage.
That's perfect.
Hey everyone. it's sophomore year.
and they just came back.
Older. wiser. flier.
Let's go!
Whoa!
What is on your face?
How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look like an assistant coach.
Oh. hey!
You sure you want to do this for me?
Did you hear what I did?
What?
If I drop you. really. how long do you
think you've been taking me into the ground?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Let's get this on a high note.
huh?
What happened?
All the evidence you're going to need is
the trunk of his car.
Are you trying to take my dog like this?
Hey. you guys are the professionals.
I'm just a volunteer.
He is a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man's prime rights have
dropped to a record low.
Police and damage control give much of the
credit to the Master Bureau.
Initiate high tests.
Armed robbery is to the Union Bank.
In the past six months. he has taken down
every major prime ward across the five
boroughs. including the super-powered
ninja crew to hand.
He is the pride of New
York City. a hero every
grown-up relies on and
every kid wants to be.
Final semester at MIT.
Oh my gosh. we're graduating in a month.
He made so many memories.
When do I begin?
I'm swimming in the Charles River with Jim
and Wiley.
The infamous food fight is
with Banana Lounge. pulling
all-nighters and studs
by with MJ and Nate Dow.
It feels like yesterday
I was sitting on a roof
with MJ dreaming about
coming here together.
I still can't believe I'm dizzy.
I'm so grateful for all the friends that
I've made.
I couldn't imagine going through this with
anyone else.
Dad. what are you thinking that you should
watch this?
Uh. I don't know.
They made it so long.
Why so long?
What?
No!
I mean.
we're talking about downtown Brooklyn in
broad daylight.
I broke my job like that. and you know
that Fazzo was involved.
Yeah. I hate you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. we're going
through his financial records
and we're following
his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know. saying you do something you
love. you don't work a day in your life.
Can't be of that.
Mom. where's my calculator?
Trust me. a'ight?
Being married to the job never ends well.
Well. don't worry about it.
I'll be okay.
Oh. yeah?
Do you still get in them headaches.
then?
Uh. yeah.
But. um... But I'll be fine.
I don't know. man.
I think your body's trying to tell you
something.
Like you need to get out of that suit
every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
No. puppy.
What you need is a real human connection.
Oh. what?
And we're not connecting?
Not. dude.
I don't know your name. your face.
or nothing about you.
I don't think you'd ever ask me a question
about my life.
Sure. I. uh... What
are my kids' names?
Uh. well. for starters. your son's name's
Poppy.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spider-Man?
Oh. gosh.
A hijack tank is heading south about past
34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work. lucky you.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
You got it!
I got you. Spider-Man!
No. no. I don't need you.
You okay. kid?
Yeah. you're okay.
You wouldn't know it just
by looking at it. but this very
street was completely destroyed
in the Battle of New Orleans.
Come on. come on!
Pull down. let's go!
Come on.
Quit your whim. Frank.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You got damn right with us.
It's time you're gonna get the hell out of
my way.
What. you mean. instead of saving your
life?
You didn't talk about that Staten Island
bullshit again.
What. you said it. not me?
Look. man. you can't
just shoot yourself out
of every situation.
innocent people get hurt.
Who do you think's downrange that tank.
young dog?
Shoot yourself.
I'm gonna kill this kid.
I'm trying.
Try harder.
There's a lot of scary boots locked up in
there.
Who do you think put them in there?
Let's go.
Uh.
get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Where am I?
I got you.
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
You know. the whole time
I've been chasing you. you
forgot to ask yourself a
very important question.
It wasn't a tank.
Spiderman?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Hey. good job.
It's okay.
Look. let these people take a ferry.
I remember right here.
I love you Spiderman.
Yeah. alright buddy. alright.
Hey. what do you got?
Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue 10
minutes later.
The guard walked him right off the door.
What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from the damage control warehouse
in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor of warfare.
You got a motive?
Not on.
And no criminal record.
Scorpion must have gotten to us somehow.
Yeah. maybe.
What do you mean. maybe?
I'm here.
I don't know.
But I know someone that might.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi.
Is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
It's 3250 Brighton Beach.
Okay.
I already think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
Uh. what?
You don't have clothes in the manual.
They just don't have time.
This is not the laboratory.
Your tech said that this was your office.
This is my office.
You didn't?
Fine. thanks.
I'll just... My
office. my rules.
This way. you get to enjoy a nice relaxing
soak.
And I get to see that you don't have any
weapons.
And we both win.
Okay.
Really?
Would you never take that off?
No. you know.
It defeats the whole honestly.
Even for your girlfriend or boyfriend?
Or whatever.
There's a lot of conjecture on it.
And super graphic artwork.
Have you seen the one with you and the ten
mysterious?
Wait. wait. wait.
I've seen it.
It's hard to unsee. to be honest.
But look. I don't have any one.
I just kind of came to myself.
Open yourself all the time?
I wonder you're so sad.
Not that so sad.
A little bit.
Can we just talk about what I came here to
talk to you about?
The attack on damage control?
Yes. so that is more your area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers are focusing on
big potato stuff.
Right. okay.
Well. there's more to it than that.
You know. the driver and the others who
were helping.
It was like someone was talking to me
through them.
Like someone was looking at me through
their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control.
Exactly.
Like how they used on me in the red room.
And the other weirdos.
Right.
No. I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably more like
possession.
Possession?
As a ghost. or a demon. or in Russia we
have leche.
Leshim rules the forest
and can possess... Sorry.
Whatever it is. then you're looking for
something.
This is the fourth attack on the damage
control facility this month.
And what do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today.
there was a cross
agency cyber security
alert that got triggered.
Someone accessed the
damage control restricted servers.
using credentials from 30
employees from the waystation.
They all searched for the same thing.
VMAX.
VMAX?
What does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tech. or secretive
weapon programs. or launch codes. or.
..
I don't know.
This is for you to figure out.
This is small baby potato stuff.
No. I think potato brain stuff.
Jeez. maybe I'll just go ask damage
control myself.
You know. you're not completely anonymous
anymore.
I've seen your belly button.
Okay.
Fine.
Alright. I got an appointment
with... Director Metzger. yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Hyphen sensus.
Exogenous DNA.
Arachnid.
Please remove your face covering for
identity scan.
Oh no. I can't do that.
A failure to remove your face covering
will result in defensive measures.
Defensive measures?
What are you doing?
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
guys. guys. guys. I can't take my mask off.
I'm sorry.
Spider-Man.
He's alright.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger. director of damage control.
How are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We have to beef up security around here.
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No. not at all.
Alright. come on this way.
This floor is mostly research and
administrative.
Downstairs we have incident cleanup.
laboratories. agent training.
Hey. what are they doing here?
It's okay.
The hand works for us now.
After you brought
them in. I realized that
fundamentally they're a
group of kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly all the things
that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable
part of our security team.
You can look at the many threats that face
us and see only danger.
But you can see opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of Shaka. these are a
nuisance.
That doesn't mean we can't buy from the
technology or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive
energy into something useful.
That's the true meaning of damage control.
Be careful with that.
Right this way.
I wanted to talk to you about the recent
attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with a threat we
can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolf's report.
I believe you understand exactly what
we're up against.
Someone knew or something that could hop
into people's minds.
But not yours.
No. I mean it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm going to be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get
in here and find whatever it
is it's looking for. the
consequences could be unimaginable.
Let me guess. is whatever it's looking for
in that giant vault?
There are some things because of the
nature of my job I cannot tell you.
But I believe you are our best defense
against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech. Director.
I'll do everything that I can.
I promise.
Well then consider yourself a friend of
damage control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Oh. I wanted to ask.
The phrase VMAX doesn't mean anything to
you. does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh. it's just. you know. nature being a
superhero.
There are some things I just can't tell
you.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great.
Keep it up.
I don't think Mascara
knows any more than we do.
but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
You want to help?
The best thing you could do is find
Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah. I know.
I have every camera in the city running a
facial recognition scandal.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably. for the past.
But look. if he shows his face.
we'll know.
You know what they need. any thanks?
None of you.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Easy.
Hey. uh. also. you got any sharp-fired
energy?
Yeah.
Oh. no. no. no.
I don't want any of them.
That's the peculiar.
You know. all my friends were drinking
them during finals. and now they're
addicted. so I'm gonna need you to not
sell me any.
Memorize my face.
Please. do not sell this guy any
sharp-fire.
Sure.
Whatever.
Actually. I'll take one.
Last one.
Maybe two.
And then never sell me any.
Oh. uh. see. you've stumbled across my
board.
I'm not one of those weirdos. I swear.
You actually saved me and my friends'
lives a few times in high school.
Oh. cool.
Yeah. yeah.
Ever since. I've just been trying to
figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the world or
anything. just to...
hopefully thank him face-to-face.
I actually created this app that monitors
his sightings.
Well. you created Spidey Tracker.
You heard of it.
Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
Well. Shadow right there.
We know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down
into prime suspects.
Yeah. if you knew where they were.
it wouldn't really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
Oh. um... There's like
50 people in an apartment.
Statistically speaking. at least two of
them are sociopaths.
Which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
Oh. they're. uh...
Housewarming.
Really?
Yeah.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
It's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm. uh... Maine.
Maineard.
Oh. you two don't know each other?
No. I'm a neighbor.
Friendly neighbor?
Sorry.
So. how was the interview?
I'm going to go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you. Maineard.
Maineard?
Maineard.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yeah. no. I went.
And?
And I got the job.
Oh my god. MJ. that's amazing.
I got the job.
What?
Yeah. I'm going to work for some solace
collaboration.
They're not all solace.
Okay. they're all mostly solace.
But don't you want. like. health
insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. but it will cost.
Depends on your deductible.
Oh. you mean like your principles?
Yes.
Sorry.
I don't know. I know it sounds cheesy.
but...
Something is just telling me that I'm
supposed to be waiting for something.
Great. you know?
Okay. um. to. uh. waiting for something
great.
Waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
Oh!
Yo!
Dude. this is top shelf!
Just like you.
Oh!
I'm gonna hide this.
I lifted this off again.
What if Ned needs the fire of a thousand
sharks?
You mean heart palpitations.
You can't save everyone.
I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry. man.
We'll begin in 10 minutes.
We should've lived together.
Yeah. for sure.
Yeah. I'd live back.
Be the first one.
Yup. we'll all be together.
Yeah. we're right here.
I'm gonna... I should start.
I'm gonna forget who I am.
I can't forget what you're talking about.
It's okay.
My
name is Peter Parker.
Is there anything else?
Come on!
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
when I've got power?
You know. this whole thing can get really
scary.
In and out.
Oh yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change.
Very quickly.
Ways that we can't even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
Oh my God.
Well. I live here.
I just don't...
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that me. Sherry?
No.
Oh. cute dog.
Hi. Peter.
You have 107 new alerts.
Please check backlog.
What is happening?
The results of your body scan show a surge
in the hormones associated with your
arachnid DNA. resulting in
the formation of organic web
spinnerets and dangerously
heightened sensory receptors.
Okay. but I feel for it.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced any recent traumatic
events?
Peter?
I'm fine. Evie.
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take some time to
rebalance.
Well. that's not really an option.
is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
What?
Alert.
Senses are overloaded.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking in too
much information at once.
Okay.
It's okay.
Alright. organic webs.
Peter. too. Adam.
He was cool.
You're cool.
Oh. my God. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs.
Come on. and web!
What's going on. Evie?
Shots fired at the Damage Control Data
Center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Come on. three. two. one.
Let's go!
Stop!
Stop.
stop. stop. stop!
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
Oh!
I'm sorry. I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
I'm scorpion. but we really gotta keep
doing this.
My head is killing me.
You think I'm scorpion?
What's happening to you?
Huh.
You can't sense me anymore.
You!
What's going on with you. Spider-Man?
Warning!
A rat-led cornball has been creasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
Give me some help over here.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
The wolf. is she hurt?
Is she okay?
No.
Just let me go!
What?
It's going back over here.
It wasn't scorpion. okay?
I mean. it was...
He was possessed by whatever.
I object to me.
Please. can I just blow that up?
Listen. I don't know what this is.
I need you to blow that together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
No. I'm sorry.
If you act like this again. I cannot
protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
I'm sorry.
Through lattice chromodynamics.
we can arrange time and space in a grid.
which allows us to simulate the quarks
binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this the question about protons.
or more stuff about adventures?
Guys. I love to tell
stories. but you know. I
gotta teach you some
physics at some point. yeah?
Alright. let it rip. Cindy.
If Vanis was so worried
about overpopulation. why
didn't you just use the magic
glove to make more food?
Arthur. do you want to answer that
question?
Whoa!
Uh. you screaming. Dr. Bennett?
I. um...
Uh. you okay?
Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to you about your
inhibitor.
Oh. sure.
Don't worry.
It's got failsafe. so I'm
not going to turn into the
big green raging monster
machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me with this thing off.
run.
No. but you're using target-specific short
interfering RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing. you're just
incorporating the gamma radiation.
What'd you say your name was?
Uh. Ned.
Gleats.
So you found a way to suppress the
expression of DNA. even as it's undergoing
the mutation due to gamma radiation.
right?
Yes.
Okay. so my question is.
would that same thing be
possible with DNA that's
mutating for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is mixed
with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically. yes. it's possible.
Yes.
So could you suppress only some parts of
that DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects. but just keep all
the good stuff?
You mean. like if I wanted to keep some
parts of home. but not others?
Right.
It would be enormously dangerous and
complex. but...
if you were able to target the correct
mRNA strand...
Possibly.
Wait. so you could just turn
the mutating gene on and
off as long as you do it
before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same thinking.
you could even develop some kind of
automatic inhibitor that would just adjust
to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking
about a universal inhibitor
that would control anyone
who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Yeah. but it's theoretical. right?
You're not one of my students.
are you?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've. uh... I've taken
enough of your time.
I gotta get some books back to the
library.
The library is that way.
Right. right.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Old parts of nature are good or bad.
What if you're trying to
control the expression
of something that
needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
Okay.
Upload inhibitor in beta-del.
Uploaded.
Would you like to run a test?
Yeah. run it.
Spiders have three stages in their life
cycle.
Each stage is characterized by physical
changes. with the largest changes
occurring during the beautiful transition
to adulthood.
For those who make it through.
molting amounts to a kinder reaper.
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Turning off video.
Inhibitor after video.
Come on. come on. come on.
Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid hormones to your
baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. Evie.
Let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert.
Inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah. I'm sensing them.
Alert.
Sensors are overloaded.
Web grenades activated.
Oh!
Inhibitor field test one.
Failure.
Yo. Spiderman!
You okay?
Yeah. I'm just trying out some new tech.
Oh. yeah.
To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me. huh?
Get your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only person I've met
that I can't... hop into.
You're sure that's really frustrating for
you?
Well. I'll get it in one day.
What do you want?
I don't know why a half-human.
half-spider would decide to work for an
organization whose one mission is to hunt
down anybody who's different.
Damage control isn't after you because
you're different.
They're hunting you down because you're
dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple spider.
let me spell it out for you.
Damage control is something that I need.
Oh. you mean V-Bags?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
Are you sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment
is kind of like a parody where
you think a sad single guy
in his twenties might live.
Take out containers. pre-weight protein
powder...
You're bluffing.
You know you're not hard to track down.
Peter.
Well. at least not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing.
though.
In the wrong places.
Coffee cup.
If you display home workstation...
You spend four years erasing Peter Parker
from existence?
No wonder the spider's trying to swallow
up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not going to let that happen.
No. her roommate was nice enough to post a
new address online.
I'll allow this.
I'll race you.
You touch her.
It'll start swinging.
I'm fast.
SUBS: CRETA STAR
Hey!
It's a long way there. MJ.
You better pick up the base.
You've been track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies between
subjects.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
In race for the love of his life.
then it's not looking good.
Come on. Spidey.
Keep up.
Sorry.
You have a limit to your jump radius.
don't you?
Thirty-three feet.
I don't see anybody else.
I'll be up here for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting me.
Hey. hey. hey!
I'm sorry for doing things.
Where's your roommate?
What?
Where's Ben?
Hey. boss. it was Frank's.
Why?
Okay. good.
You gotta come with me.
I don't know if you're the real Spider-Man
or coming with you.
You don't have time for this.
Please. come on.
You need to get out of my apartment.
Look. this is going to
sound insane. but there is
someone who is after you
who is really dangerous. okay?
And I promised you that I would keep you
safe.
Please. you just have to trust me.
Come on.
Fine.
Where are you staying?
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay.
We should be safe up here.
Okay. we'll see from what?
Uh. I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
I don't know.
You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
Um. I wish I could tell you.
I just...
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me
crazy for years. all the
times that Spider-Man
saved either me or Ned.
It was the Washington
Monument. and then it
was London. and Prague.
and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice as a coincidence.
but over and over again.
We knew each other.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Wait. you're wrong?
What were we?
Were we classmates. or friends.
or something?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just... I can't remember. and I feel
like someone scrambled my brain.
and you're the only one who would know
why.
This is crazy. and I think... I
know that you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of me that still
remembers.
This is too so funny.
I can't believe that you figured it out.
I did.
Hold on.
You've been wanting to do this alone?
True love's kiss breaks the spell.
and reunites to serve cross-lovers.
I'm Jamie Vomit.
You really are a simple spider.
aren't you?
See why you like her?
She's. uh... She's smart.
A little dark and twisted.
I mean. it is sad.
There is. like. no thoughts of you in
here.
Once over.
But you knew that. didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you love someone more
than I love her. then you
know that what you're doing
right now is unforgivable.
Oh. is that so?
You know. some people who killed told a
person they loved one last time.
I am.
You're running out of time. Peter.
So they know it won't just be your friends
who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should write a letter to
yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
MJ!
No. no. no.
Oh. God.
Oh. God. please. no.
Come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Oh. thank God.
Oh. you're okay.
I'm so sorry.
Stop!
Wait. wait. stop!
Please!
Oh. quick!
You win!
Just don't hurt her!
You're a mess. Spider-Man.
Any time I want.
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect MJ.
Even for herself.
It really is a nice letter.
A little heavy-handed.
I'm not bad.
I'm gonna take you someplace safe.
Take me to 3165.
Navigating to Empire State University.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay. I'm saving you a picture.
You're okay.
Fine. fine.
Can we just slow down for like two
seconds. please?
We're almost there.
Yeah. yeah. but you just told me I was
mind-controlled.
Well. not kidding.
If you're lucky. I believe in that stuff.
okay?
Because governments have been doing it for
years. especially the French.
Are you okay?
Yeah. look. sorry.
I'm just trying to take you someplace
safe. okay?
I don't feel safe.
You're losing it. kid.
Don't you be able to see that coming a
mile away.
What is wrong with you?
You couldn't kill us.
Excuse me?
You showed up to my house. and now it's
what he thinks is gonna happen.
Wait. this is your house?
What the hell is that?
What the hell are you?
Uh. uh. she's. um. uh... you know.
No. I don't know.
That's why I just asked.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
Yeah. it looks like it.
Oh. come on.
You owe me.
Ah. fuck.
That's your synchronous story.
That's an island.
That's that island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid.
I got to save it twice to get a picture.
That guy didn't even hit me with a handful
of rice.
What does that sound like to you?
I have exactly what I wanted.
I see the idea.
I know exactly what I feel.
Okay. fine.
Go ahead.
What does that sound like to you?
I don't care.
I just want to go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks.
No. no. wait. wait.
Quick. quick. quick. quick. quick.
Please.
Have God to keep her safe. okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right.
Just watch out for the clay mortar.
I want to pick up pieces of you for the
next two weeks.
Hey. I definitely would not eat that
chili.
So you're telling me
that maniac behind all that
tank nonsense is nothing
but a goddamn teenager.
And it's not just a tank.
It's every attack on damage control this
past month.
How does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know. Frank.
Beat your ass all over the street like
that.
She did not beat my ass.
Is this your family?
You should get the hell away from that.
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything.
You sure as shit don't ask me any goddamn
questions about anything.
So three rules.
I see why you like her.
Go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
Of course you don't.
So I managed to pull this image from my
hut and run it through the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple months ago.
Nobody.
She was in and out of foster
care. psych hospitals. and
then eventually she ran
away and dropped off her grip.
It's hardly any information
about her that hasn't
been scrubbed. but she's
classified as a telepath.
And now we have a name.
Jean Grey.
You know. these are the damage control
sites that she hasn't hit yet.
So if she surfaces. then my facial
tracking program will pick her up.
Right.
Oh yeah?
What then?
Well. don't worry about what then.
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it. huh?
I'm just supposed to sit here and babysit
your girlfriend?
I don't want to.
She's my baby's dad.
Alright. look. what's the plan.
huh?
She's got a hope that your facial tracking
program works.
You get yourself killed. I gotta watch her
the rest of my life.
I'm not gonna get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just have to fix my inhibitor and then
I'll be good to go.
Then what do you need to do that?
Frank. you do not have what I need to do
that. okay?
Hey. I've got something out for you.
What. do you think you have an
anti-static. Matt?
A total probe with micro-tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe to maybe call
someone and let them know I'm okay?
Like your boyfriend?
No. like my roommate.
Oh. um... I don't think that's
such a good idea. you know?
Because she already knows who he is and
she can inhabit anyone she wants.
so... Yeah. yeah.
yeah. you're right.
Sorry.
No. it's fine.
I totally get it.
Like all my boyfriend. he just asked me a
bunch of questions that I couldn't answer
and um... he'd tell me I
was being withholding again.
Withholding?
Yep.
Sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a
jerk.
Well. why do you think you're withholding?
I don't know.
He'd tell me Mass Vigilante behind the
curtain.
Um. okay. I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have Mrs. Spiderman?
Do I have Mrs. Spiderman?
Um... No. no.
Why not?
Because um...
I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
Hello?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I uh...
I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
I'm sorry. that must have been really hard
for you.
Yeah. it was. yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm okay.
You know what?
It's gonna come over... Hold on.
hold on. hold on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
Um. it just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace. I was gonna
major in biochemical engineering. so...
Do you mind if I...
Oh. yeah. for sure.
Here.
Here you go.
Wow.
So. does the device
itself... I mean. does it
generate any kind of
radiation or a magnetic field?
Because that would definitely interfere.
Well. yeah. it has a micro-magnetic field.
but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
Oh. it actually dissipates into the
fabric. which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles... or whatever you call them.
Uh. they would create a field.
It would be tiny. but... But it's on your
head. which is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
Oh. and that is genius.
Okay. that's the work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. that feels better.
That feels totally better.
Oh. my head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
Oh my god. Angie. that totally worked.
You know. this isn't really intense stuff
you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like... I mean.
this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the kind of stuff you put
on. like. I don't know. like a monster?
Well. if you see what's
been happening to me over
the last couple days.
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with you for the last
few hours. and that's not what I've seen.
Well. what have you seen?
Through my side of the curve.
A really good guy.
It might just be changing.
I don't mean to overstep.
I'll. uh. lead it back to it.
Can't sleep either. huh?
You want coffee?
Sure.
Did you shift fix?
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean. it should
completely shut down her powers.
Yeah. what else would work?
You'd just shoot her.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
That has got to be the coolest shit I've
ever seen in my life.
But you can't even take the mask off.
Drink a cup of coffee?
I'll take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she kidding?
I don't know.
Ah. that's horseshit.
Who is she?
I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
You care about her.
You don't care about her.
I don't care about her.
Look. I don't know who she is.
Frank. okay?
I don't have anybody.
I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me.
Well. you know about me. kid.
You think this is a choice?
Living like this is a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
You know something?
If I had one second. people I love are
still breathing.
You think I'm behind behind a mask?
You think I pretend to be something that
I'm not?
Acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial manage.
She's at the Damage Control HQ in
Manhattan.
I gotta go.
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Thanks. Frank.
Hey.
She's gonna let him go himself.
You know. I think he might need you.
Hey.
Kinda like you needed him. was that that?
You can't hide from me forever.
Bill.
You've got a strong door. but it's the
wall you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Grey.
And you know what I want.
Come on.
Jean.
You woke me up?
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen to your girl
if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
You're definitely not getting inside that
vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know what you're dealing
with.
You know. you and Banner have a lot in
common.
We're fighting the losing battle against
the monster that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk you can't just...
What the hell?
Oh. I see.
Trying to muzzle me like you muzzle
yourself.
I can't let you in there.
Whatever VMAX is. you're not getting it.
I can't help it. man.
Jean. don't do this.
Frank. what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
I think I'm doing it.
I'm stealing your ass.
I think it's way to close your papers.
Get out of here!
Stop shooting him!
You're out of your fucking mind!
He said it's not the problem!
She is!
I thought I told you to stay home and
watch MJ.
Yes. you did.
Then she tells me I gotta come watch you.
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing that for Bill?
You're blushing that?
God dammit. I knew you were supposed to
pick a gun.
That's a good idea. bring a bigger gun.
What are you gonna do. pick one to death?
No. look. change your plan.
First we get this on the Hulk.
then we go after G.
I got one better.
That's the highest casualty producing
trip.
You contain it.
I will find this towards I take it down.
You got it?
Are you just trying to get out of finding
the Hulk?
I guess so.
Okay. whatever dude. I got this.
What the fuck are you doing?
Do not kill her!
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
No. stop. I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do
it my way.
Just go!
Don't get within 33 feet!
So frustrating!
Hey.
Oh shit.
Whoa.
This guy's got issues.
Oh no.
No. nobody can.
Dr. Banner?
Is that you?
Spiderman.
What happened?
Did I do all this?
Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault.
She was in your mind.
She wasn't in control.
Here. here.
It's okay.
I got another one.
I just need you to put this on.
It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please. sir.
There's people in the building.
Just put it on.
You okay?
My head.
I think she broke something.
Is she still in there?
No.
It's the other guy.
Bruce?
I could get you out of here. okay?
I just need you to put that inhibitor on.
I can't get you.
Yes. you can. Bruce.
Yes. you can.
Get out of the building!
Don't!
Santa. please!
Look at me!
Don't!
Hold me home!
I didn't know you could get that big.
Well. good luck with that. Peter.
No!
There you are.
Just hold still!
I'm
going to leave her out.
I'm to detonation.
Don't you think I'm going to detonation?
I know!
Why is your skin so thin?
Inhibitor's head on
it.
It's Weaver.
I'll be your friend.
Throw down your guns. or you'll get the
next one in the head.
Where is she?
It's over. Jane.
It's over.
Is that her?
It's in my gun.
Is anyone hurt?
Is this Steve?
Spider-Man!
You saved my life.
You saved God knows how
many lives. but I'm making
sure she didn't find what
she was looking for in there.
Before she passed out. she tried to say
something.
A name. Sarah.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her. she
managed to get in my mind for a moment.
Sarah was the name of someone I worked
closely with every single past.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of Sarah must have
affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk to her when she
wakes up.
If that's all right.
Of course.
She'll be transferred to our facility on
Roosevelt Island.
I'm just as eager to give a talking as you
are.
Well. let's not strain her too much for
one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
Okay.
Good work.
She's in custody.
Are you safe now?
You left this?
Did you want me to find it?
No.
Um... Look. I can explain.
Can you take that off. please?
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this
conversation with Peter Parker.
He came to the party at our apartment the
other night.
In the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
Oh. I've almost been
killed like five times the
past 24 hours. so it's not
really working that well.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right.
So you just were gonna make that decision
for me.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to keep saying
that.
You're sorry.
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
I want you to tell me why you would do
this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be here if that wasn't
for me.
I can read you that letter because I didn't
want anything like that to happen to you.
That's not really your decision.
I know it's not. but you mean everything
to me.
And I've been trying to live my life
without you. but I can't.
I love you.
This spell. or whatever it is that you
did. it worked.
All these memories that you're saying that
we have together. I don't...
I don't have them.
And I do see why. you
know. she would love
you. the girl you wrote
that letter to. but...
I understand that you did what you had to
do to protect her.
And for that. I'm so grateful.
But I... I don't love you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Yeah. sure.
I've been a while.
Oh yeah?
Yeah. of course.
Do you want to come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. maybe?
I would love that.
The Hulk. a.k.a.
Dr. Bruce Banner. is in custody. currently
being transferred to a psychiatric ward.
After years as a peaceful academic.
the question the world asked today is.
what finally snapped?
Huh?
Hey. I'm nearby.
And Dave?
Yeah.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Uh. you're not going to believe this.
But the Spidey Tracker app says that
Spider-Man is in the direct facility.
Oh yeah?
No way. that's crazy.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Uh. Ned?
Spider-Man?
Ned?
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
I'm not. like. a weirdo or anything.
He's a little weird.
Why. uh. why are you here?
Oh. I. uh... I was
on a subway...
...platform. right. and she was on her
phone.
Yeah. I got a little distracted and the
train was coming.
And I just swooped her right up.
Oh my God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So. what if you're mid-swing and you
decide to need to pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down the ground level and run
into a coffee shop?
And you're like. you don't spider-man I
need to pee.
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a rooftop somewhere.
Ned.
Is this really what you want to be asking
him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
You can ask me anything.
You want to know how my web shooters work?
I mean. I already know how the web
shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously
some sort of sheer thinning
fluid that is cycling
within a chamber. right?
So you can keep it slippery for them.
And then when you
activate it by pressing on
the triggers. it runs
through a Teflon turbine.
And then. it hardens when it interacts
with the air. right?
I mean. not exactly. but... Okay. okay.
well then tell me what's in the web fluid.
I would guess something like a long-chain
polymer nylon.
It's pretty close.
Okay. okay.
What about Nomex or... oh. Kevlar!
Alright. then keep those secrets.
If you are very good at the incident with
the dragon. I was barely involved.
All I did was simply give your uncle and
his little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Ooh. bondme time!
You ordered bondmes?
I ordered five bondmes.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's gonna get fat.
Sorry about him.
He's just. like. very excited that you're
here.
Are you kidding?
This is. like. the most fun I've had in
years.
I really miss you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
When she was inhabiting you on the rooftop.
she kissed me. and I kissed her back.
Because I thought it was you. but I didn't
know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like I remember anything
anyway. so...
Really?
Yeah.
It was weird.
It was. like. one second
I was sitting at my desk.
and the next second I
was lying on the street.
I don't know. like. a light switch went
off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. why?
Metzger said he remembered thinking about
someone named Sarah. but what you're
saying is that you don't remember anything
at all.
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you called Leshy.
Yeah. my name's Jean Grey.
I need some help determining the size of
some potatoes.
Potatoes?
I think that's my without.
I think Metzger lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Sarah?
Hmm. his potatoes sound meager.
Oh. wow.
That really is your own place.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records.
and a lot of data related
to Jean Grey has been
scrubbed by damage control.
They never what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister.
Hmm.
Sarah Grey.
Also. a telepath.
Damage control took her into custody for
study and observation.
I mean. you can probably guess what they
mean by that.
Spearmitation and other human rights
violations?
Yes. exactly.
Wait. who are you?
Hi. that means...
Hi!
I'm sorry. I... I'm just so happy
that this sad man has friends.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye.
She was just looking for her sister. and
I handed her to the people who took her.
I gotta go.
Hey. Peter?
Yeah.
You should be careful. all right?
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her.
Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You gonna hop?
First. pick someone close.
And then...
Each hop has a limit. but...
you can string them together and go as far
as you want.
And when you let go...
you're right back where you started.
Could you do that to everyone in this park
at once?
Yeah. maybe one day.
You get really good.
Now could you just...
send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that. anyway.
She was.
Before we changed.
Yeah. well. if that's
all it takes for you
to stop being a mom.
then you're not a mom.
What would you do if you had daughters
like us?
I'd love them.
Especially the redhead.
Shut up.
We have each other.
You think we have ice cream?
On the chip or chocolate?
Subject is awake.
Heart rate is 94 BPM.
Jean. that's not going to work anymore.
Thanks to Spiderman.
Jean.
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay?
You're safe.
Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister. you've
been blessed with a power that
has the potential to do
tremendous good in the world.
Or tremendous damage.
The power like yours in the hands of a
child is an impossible burden.
But imagine...
if that power was placed in the hands of
people who actually know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're going to change the world.
Jean.
Hey!
Go!
You've got eyes everywhere. kid.
Look. Frank. everything's all kidnapped
Jean's sister.
Jean was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
It's sentimental horse shit.
You see what she can do and what she's
capable of.
What. you're going to let her loose?
Is that what you're going to do?
I can tell you right now. you do that.
I ain't going to run my way.
Frank. please get out of here.
Frank!
This is Joe.
Forty foot clearance.
Lock and down the room.
Lock and down.
Disengage inevitable.
Change of power is enough for the
operation.
As you can tell. we're beyond your jump
rates.
Tell me what VMAX is.
You're the second person to ask me about
that.
I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you telepathically
across all that distance.
We did register a huge spike in that
session.
Fascinating.
What does it mean. asshole?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
I work with Sarah Stenchen on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power and
identifying her path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a
telepathic brain during a jump.
then perhaps we could replicate those
pathways in the mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We build this together over many months of
trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what VMAX is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Coffee.
We're in full lockdown.
The process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa. that's a pretty serious look
there. dude.
Hey. whoa. what the hell. man?
Come on. I'm afraid of damage.
Control. what are you doing?
Huh. it's gonna be like that if you wanna
go.
Alright. alright. just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Did you stretch?
Are you a big stretcher?
I mean. you should do it.
You're a lot of work.
What about you?
Are you guys stretched?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Where is Jean Grey?
This is jump 26.
Recordings look good.
Excuse me. sir.
We have an entry.
You were right.
She's much stronger than a sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well. Jean.
Jean?
Jean. can you hear me?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are evolving.
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this
room.
The brain waves are somehow affecting the
object. so I'm gonna shut it down.
I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister saw was this
goddamn room!
Shut it down!
I can't. sir.
I can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hands that will wield this power
are mine.
What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sarah.
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here to save a helpless girl
from damage control. you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now. so are you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
Get in. please!
Fuck!
Isn't it funny how your friends from
damage control developed a special...
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
Any more than they trust you.
Frank.
Good phone. kid.
Just gotta hold everyone within a
kilometer of the island.
Wait. what?
Look. if you're gonna do something.
you better do it now.
Damn it.
My sister died in this room.
Surrounded by these men.
And her only crime was that she was
special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't get to live a normal
life.
We don't get to have friends.
Or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just be honest with
yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Jean. please.
This won't make it right.
Come on. you're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her felt like he
lost everything.
If you come any closer. he dies!
They hold you!
You know this won't bring her back.
right Jean?
Don't be so sure I can't get into your
mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last
tried.
Hey.
I think you don't have to listen to me and
I've got powers.
You know. this whole thing can get really
scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't even imagine right now.
I know.
No.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really great about yourself.
But I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it'll be really lonely.
And sometimes. because you're special.
people can do dark. monstrous things to you.
But. this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful.
And the people who love you. we love you.
Not because you're special. we love you.
But because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels like you're totally
alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that. no matter how
powerfully they come.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would have loved her.
Just because we've lost someone.
It doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean. we can.
Trust me. I'm sorry.
We have been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true.
I have no one.
You have me?
You are?
Fine.
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter!
No. no. no. Peter!
You gotta get out of here.
Don't be looking for me.
No. no. no. no. no.
Please just stay with me.
Come on. hold on. come on. please!
Peter!
Just go.
Look at me.
A Spider-Man arrived at Bellevue Hospital
with a bullet wound.
Seemingly a death story.
The reclusive crime
fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical
experts work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved
New York so many times is
now in the hands of
its best and brightest.
And the people of New
York hold their breath.
No. no. no. no. no. hey.
Where's my mask?
Someone left there. I got you covered.
You're good.
Where is she?
Is she okay?
Yeah. she's okay.
She's okay.
Where is she?
I think maybe she just left.
She was using her magic voodoo shit to
keep you alive.
Yeah. she's alright.
I'm sorry.
Frank.
Just. just. I'm really sorry for what I
did.
No. Frank.
I know there's a lot of things.
but it sure shit ain't okay. alright?
I see.
I see real bravery.
I see that you killed my day.
But that happened.
That was something else.
You crying?
No. I ain't crying.
No. you look exactly where I thought you
would.
A nice kid.
I did.
Never had a friend like that.
Only friends now.
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
I didn't cry like I'm talking about it.
Bullshit.
Oh. yeah.
I've been doing it all night.
Been here since you walked in.
Just take a look.
Yo. kid.
You came in there to cut through the suit.
But when you're ready to split.
I got a plan.
Hey!
It's Spider-Man!
I've been thinking a lot about what you
said.
And you'd be happy to
know that I've decided I'm
not... I'm not going to
do this alone anymore.
Don't miss you. mate.
I mean. I still got a little
pain in my back. but I could
probably get back out there
if you need me for a minute.
But what I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know.
But come on. you got to give me something.
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. Mexico's still missing.
But your friend. Black Widow. she's been
helping us.
They do all the records.
Damage control tried to have scrubbed.
Had me drop by her office. the other day.
And how was that?
Well. uh. my skin feels amazing.
Attention all units.
We have a confirmed bank robbery in
progress.
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that hard for me.
I could probably meet you down.
No. we can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to E.J.
Marley for me.
Okay.
Spiderman says hello.
Hi.
Uh. hey.
Oh. uh. flower guy. right?
From the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay. hello.
SUBS: CRETA STAR
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm